welabs.com.br 2017-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Media Temple

Effective Date: 06/20/2016

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to www.mediatemple.net (the “Site” or “Media Temple”) owned and operated by Go Daddy Operating Company LLC. It describes how Media Temple collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information.

### **EU-U.S. Privacy Shield**

Our parent company, Go Daddy Operating Company, LLC (and our related entities, including GoDaddy.com, LLC, Wild West Domains, LLC, Blue Razor Domains, LLC, Starfield Technologies, LLC, Domains by Proxy, LLC, Outright, Inc., Locu, Inc. and Mad Mimi, Inc.) participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Go Daddy Operating Company, LLC is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework's applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's [Privacy Shield List.](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list)

Media Temple is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Media Temple complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Media Temple is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Media Temple may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at [ https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

### **A. Personally-Identifiable Information:**

Media Temple typically receives specific data about its website visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors request information, purchase or enroll for services, open a customer support inquiry ticket, provide resume information for employment opportunities, or send us e-mail. Of course, some of these activities require that you give us information, such as when you make a purchase, use a credit card to pay for services, submit your resume, or request certain types of information. When you provide personally-identifiable information to Media Temple through one of our websites, it will be used to fulfill your specific request. In most cases, you will be given the opportunity to select whether you do, or do not, want Media Temple to use this information for additional purposes.

Media Temple will not, however, sell or trade your personally-identifiable information unless we are authorized or legally required to do so, or in the case of imminent physical harm to the visitor or others. In certain situations, Media Temple may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [legal.notices@mediatemple.net](mailto:legal.notices@mediatemple.net).

We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. On those Media Temple sites where you may provide Media Temple with credit card or other sensitive information via the web, Media Temple protects and secures this information by employing commercially customary web-based security and encryption protocols, examples of which include Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and Secure Electronic Transaction (SET).

#### **Targeted Advertisements**

Absent any instructions from you, Media Temple may use information you provide to inform you about additional services and products offered by the Media Temple family of companies, Media Temple venture companies, Media Temple authorized agents, and other goods and services providers with whom Media Temple has relationships and whose offerings might be of interest to you. Media Temple and our third party partners may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) [or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)]. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

#### **Supplementation of Information**

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personally identifiable information you submit to us with information from third party sources (e.g., information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service). We do this to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our products and services to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

#### **Opt-out**

Media Temple customers control how and when we contact you by logging into the [Account Center](https://ac.mediatemple.net/) and changing your preferences. Media Temple reserves the right, in its discretion, to send you bulletins and other important information about your Media Temple services. If you are not a Media Temple customer and wish not to be emailed about our services, please click the unsubscribe link in the email you have received.

### **B. Non Personally-Identifiable (Generic) Information:**

In general, Media Temple gathers some generic information automatically. Generic information does not reveal the identity of the visitor. It usually includes information about the Internet address assigned to your computer, the number and frequency of visitors, and the Media Temple sites visited. Media Temple gathers this information for the limited purpose of determining customer service and website needs. Our Site uses cookies to identify you so you don't need to log in each time you visit our Site. The cookies are linked to your customer identifier, which is associated with the information in your account. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site and applications, but your ability to use some features or areas may be limited.

Within our Site we and our partners, affiliates, and/or analytics or service providers use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual or aggregated basis.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and/or clickstream data. We use this information gathered about you from our Site to help personalize search results, diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our Site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

We also use tracking technologies such as: CI codes (click tracking), ISC (source tracking), and ITC (item tracking codes, attached to purchases at an item level, used to determine where within the application a product was added). We report this data back to our Media Temple web services. These results are not shared with any third parties and are used solely for deciding when to retire SDKs/OS versions and to identify characteristics of major users so that we may optimize our applications and services for those user types.

With your express consent, we may access and track location data from your mobile device in order to personalize results such as user favorite domain name selections. We do not tie any personally identifiable information about you to any of the location tracking technologies that we use.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and you can refuse it; this may however reduce functionality of certain website features such as the order system and the [Account Center](https://ac.mediatemple.net/).

### **C. Your (mt) Media Temple hosted website, server, bulletin boards, forum, Third-Party Sites:**

Information that you disclose in a public space, including on any blog, bulletin board, chat room, or website Media Temple may host for you as part of your Media Temple services, is available to anyone else who visits that space. Media Temple cannot safeguard any information you disclose in these locations. Additionally, Media Temple websites contain links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to Media Temple. Media Temple cannot protect any information you may disclose in these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you visit.

On those sites where you voluntarily offer any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas or the like, Media Temple will treat that portion of the information as non-confidential and nonproprietary and, except as otherwise expressed in this Policy, Media Temple assumes no obligation to protect such information from disclosure. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [legal.notices@mediatemple.net](mailto:legal.notices@mediatemple.net). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

#### **Lucky Orange Web Analytics Service**

This site uses the Lucky Orange analytics system to help improve usability and the customer experience. Lucky Orange may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity. Lucky Orange may record keystroke information that you voluntarily enter on this website. Lucky Orange does not track this activity on any site that does not use the Lucky Orange system. You can choose to disable the Lucky Orange Service at <http://www.luckyorange.com/disable.php>. Note, that doing so will disable other features of the Lucky Orange system that this site employs such as 1-to-1 support chat.

### **D. Exceptions and Limitations:**

Notwithstanding the foregoing and in compliance with applicable laws, Media Temple (i) cooperates fully with state, local, and federal officials in any investigation relating to any content (including personal or private electronic communications transmitted to Media Temple) or purported unlawful activities of any user of the Service, and (ii) takes reasonable measures to protect its proprietary rights. For the limited purposes of accomplishing such cooperation and measures and in compliance with applicable laws, Media Temple may be required to disclose personally identifiable information. In addition, Media Temple may elect to monitor the areas of communication of any kind (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate Media Temple; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Media Temple or others. In connection with the potential sale or transfer of any of its interest in mediatemple.net, and ac.mediatemple.net and other sites owned by the company, Media Temple reserves the right to sell or transfer your information (including, but not limited to name, address information, and other information you provided to Media Temple) to a third party that (i) concentrates its business in communication products or services; (ii) agrees to be Media Temple's successor in interest with regard to the maintenance and protection of information collected and maintained by Media Temple; and (iii) agrees to the obligations of this Policy.

### **E. Transfer of Data Abroad:**

If you are visiting this site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers.

### **F. Access:**

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us at [legal.notices@mediatemple.net](mailto:legal.notices@mediatemple.net).

You may also correct or request deletion of your personal information by contacting us at [legal.notices@mediatemple.net](mailto:legal.notices@mediatemple.net) or through the (mt) Account Center (for instructions, [ click here](https://mediatemple.net/community/products/dv/204643030/managing-your-contact-information#/Adding_and_modifying_Contacts).)

We will respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe.

### **G. Updates:**

We may update this Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
